Guide to the Montana State University Extension Service Records 1912-1970
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- County and Home Demonstration Agents Annual Reports, 1916-1970; 1
  - Cascade County; Theo. Fosse, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Cascade County; Dora C. Smith, H.D.A.; Florence Elliott, Asst. H.D.A., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Cascade County; Theodore Fosse, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Cascade County; Dora Smith, Florence Elliott, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Cascade County; T. H. Fosse, Marian Moline, Florence Elliott, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Cascade County; Theodore Fosse, Marian Moline, Florence Elliott, 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 12-13)
  - Cascade County; Ted Fosse, James Par, Marian Moline, Florence Elliott, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Cascade County; Theodore Fosse, Marian Moline, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Cascade County; Ted Fosse, Marian Moline, Florence Elliott, Floyd A. Cranston, Joseph W. Morris, Gladys Scott, Dorothy Hixson, Ruth Poetter, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Cascade County; Fosse, Moline, Elliott, Morris, Poetter, Klosterboer, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Cascade County; Theo. Fosse, Joe Morris, Florence Elliott, Marian Moline, Myrtle Flaskerud, Carol Helterline, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Cascade County; Ted Fosse, Agent; Marian Moline, H.D.A.; Joe Morris, Assoc; Myrtle Flaskerud, JoAnne Fulbright, Lois Stephens, Assoc. H.D.A.s, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Cascade County; Theo. Fosse, Marian Moline, Joseph Morris, Lois Stephens, Anton Sundsted, N. Stillings, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Cascade County; Fosse, Morris, Sunsted, Ranney, Baringer, Moline, Stephens, Del Guerra, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Cascade County; Theodore Fosse, John Baringer, Marion Moline, Lois Stephens, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Cascade County; Theodore Fosse, James M. Ross, Marion Moline, Lois Stephens, Jack Baringer, Martha Olsen, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cascade County; Theodore Fosse, Lois K. Stephens, Marion Moline, Patricia Lewis, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Cascade County; Theodore Fosse, Lois K. Stephens, Marvin Vincent, Marion Moline, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Cascade County; Tedd Fosse, Bill Chiesa, Marion Moline, Lois Stephens, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Cascade County, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 5-8)
  - Chouteau County; W. O. Whitcomb, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Chouteau County; Wm. R. Shinn, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Chouteau County; Arthur J. Ogaard, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Chouteau County; D. W. Jones, Jr., 1920-1922 (Box 12, Folder 12-14)
  - Chouteau County; Charles H. Ruzicka, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Chouteau County; John C. Paugh, Chas. H. Ruzicka, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Chouteau County; John C. Paugh, C.A., 1925-1928 (Box 12, Folder 17-20)
  - Chouteau County; G. A. Rassley, C.A., 1929-1933 (Box 12, Folder 21-25)
  - Chouteau County; G. A. Rassley, 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 26-27)
  - Chouteau County; O. A. Lammers, Ass't Agt., 1935 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Chouteau County; G. A. Rassley, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Chouteau County; G. A. Rassley, M. J. Peterson, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Chouteau County; M. J. Peterson, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Chouteau County; M. J. Peterson, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Chouteau County; M. J. Peterson, C.A., 1940 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Chouteau County; Martin J. Peterson, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Chouteau County; Claris Brown, H.D.A., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Chouteau County; M. J. Peterson, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Chouteau County; Claris Brown, H.D.A., 1942 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Chouteau County; Jack McLean, C.A., 1943 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Chouteau County; Claris Brown, H.D.A., 1943 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Chouteau County; Jack McLean, A. L. Johnson, C.A.s, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Chouteau County; Mary Kay Mortag, H.D.A., 1944 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Chouteau County; A. L. Johnson, C.A., 1945 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Chouteau County; Mary Kay Mortag, H.D.A. - 12/1/44-6/1/45; Gale Ueland, H.D.A. - 8/1/45-11/30/45, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Chouteau County; Jack McLean, C.A.; H. B. Willson, C.A., 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Chouteau County; Fort Benton- Miss Gale Ueland, H.D.A., 1946 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Chouteau County; H. B. Willson, C.A., 1947 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Chouteau County; Gale Ueland, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Chouteau County; H. B. Willson, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Chouteau County; Mary Willick, H.D.A., 1948 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Chouteau County; H. B. Willson, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Chouteau County; Mary E. Willick, H.D.A., 1949 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Chouteau County; Keith Newby, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Chouteau County; Mary Willick, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Chouteau County; Dec. 1, 1950- June 30, 1951, Keith Newby, Mary Willick (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Chouteau County; Leland P. Cade, Minnetta L. King, 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 24-25)
  - Chouteau County; Leland P. Cade, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 26-27)
  - Chouteau County; Leland P. Cade, Juanita Stearns, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 28-29)
  - Chouteau County; Leland P. Cade, C.A.; Larry Thayer, Acting Agent; Juanita Works, H.D.A., 1958 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Chouteau County; Leland Cade, Agent; Larry Thayer, Acting Agent, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Chouteau County; Leland P. Cade, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Chouteau County; Leland P. Cade, C. Arthur Lyman, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Chouteau County; Leland P. Cade, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 34-35)
  - Chouteau County; George H. Erickson, Edison E. Martin, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Chouteau County; George Erickson, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 37-38)
  - Chouteau County, 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 39-42)
  - Custer County; M. L. Wilson, 1913-1914 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Custer County; J. C. Taylor, 1915-1916 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Custer County; C. M. Yerrington, 1917-1920 (Box 13, Folder 45-48)
  - Custer County; C. M. Yerrington, 1921-1924 (Box 14, Folder 1-4)
  - Custer County; P. M. Lewis, C.A., 1925-1929 (Box 14, Folder 5-9)
  - Custer County; P. M. Lewis, W. H. Lamphere, C.A.s, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Custer and Powder River Counties; W. H. Lamphere, C.A., 1931-1934 (Box 14, Folder 11-14)
  - Custer and Powder River Counties; William D. Ross, Willard Lamphere, N. A. Jacobsen, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Custer and Powder River Counties; N. A. Jacobsen, C.A., 1936-1945 (Box 14, Folder 16-25)
  - Custer and Powder River Counties; A. C. Kegel, C.A.; N. A. Jacobsen, C.A., 1946 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Custer and Powder River Counties; A. C. Kegel, C.A., 1947 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Custer County; Nina L. Hammock, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Custer and Powder River Counties; A. C. Kegel, C.A., 1948 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Custer County; Nina L. Hammock, H. D. A, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Custer and Powder River Counties; A. C. Kegel, 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 31-32)
  - Custer County; Rhua Slavens, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Custer and Powder River Counties; A. C. Kegel, Rhua Kepferle, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Custer and Powder River Counties; A. C. Kegel, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 35-36)
  - Custer and Powder River Counties; A. C. Kegel, Allene Willson, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 37-38)
  - Custer and Powder River Counties; A. C. Kegel, Dale Bergland, Allene Willson, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Custer and Powder River Counties; A. C. Kegel, Allene Willson, Dale Bergland, John Coston, Frankie Hougaard, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Custer County; Allene Willson, H.D.A.; A. C. Kegel, C.A., 1958 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Custer County; Allene Willson, H.D.A.; A. C. Kegel, C.A., 1959 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Custer County; Allene Willson, Arthur Kegel, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Custer County; Allene Willson, A. C. Kegel, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Custer County; Arthur C. Kegel, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Custer County; Art Kegel, Martha Olsen, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Custer County; Martha Bingham, Art Kegel, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Custer County; Art Kegel, Betty McClure, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Custer County; Betty Steiner, A. C. Kegel, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Custer County, 1967-1970 (Box 15, Folder 11-14)
  - Daniels County; A. W. Warden, C.A., 1922-1925 (Box 15, Folder 15-18)
  - Daniels County; F. H. Smith, A. W. Warden, C.A.s, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Daniels County; F. H. Smith, C.A., 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 20-21)
  - Daniels County; Vesta Hanson, H.D.A., 1928 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Daniels County; F. H. Smith, C.A., 1929 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Daniels County; Vesta Hanson, H.D.A., 1929 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Daniels County; F. H. Smith, C.A., 1930 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Daniels County; Vesta Hanson, H.D.A., 1930 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Daniels County; F. H. Smith, C.A., 1931 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Daniels County; Ada Wort, H.D.A., 1931 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Daniels County; H. M. Oefstos, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Daniels County; H. L. Dusenberry, Emergency Report, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Daniels County; George L. Hart, 1935-1937 (Box 15, Folder 31-33)
  - Daniels County; E. W. Bjork, 1938-1939 (Box 15, Folder 34-35)
  - Daniels County; E. F. Kempton, C.A., 1940-1941 (Box 15, Folder 36-37)
  - Daniels County; E. F. Kempton, R. R. Hughs, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Daniels County; R. R. Hughs, C.A., 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 39-40)
  - Daniels County; Ralph E. Briggs, C.A., 1945 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Daniels County; D. L. Allen, C.A., 1946 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Daniels County; Ralph E. Briggs, C.A., 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 43-44)
  - Daniels County; Arthur W. Carter, 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 45-46)
  - Daniels County; Arthur W. Carter, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Daniels County; Alexander Haburchak, 1952-1954 (Box 16, Folder 2-4)
  - Daniels County; Alexander Haburchak, Frances Brink, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
  - Daniels County; Alexander Haburchak, Frances Brink, Eleanor V. Harmon, Carol Ann Bradshaw, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Daniels County; Alexander Haburchak, C.A.; Carol Bradshaw, H.D.A., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Daniels County; Alexander Haburchak, C.A., 1959-1963 (Box 16, Folder 9-13)
  - Daniels County; Alexander Haburchak, Lee R. Rovig, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Daniels County; Lee R. Rovig, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 15-16)
  - Daniels County, 1967-1970 (Box 16, Folder 17-20)
  - Dawson County; J. C. Taylor, C.A., 1914 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Dawson County; George E. Piper, C.A., 1915-1916 (Box 16, Folder 22-23)
  - Dawson County; D. W. Mendenhall, C.A., 1917-1922 (Box 16, Folder 24-29)
  - Dawson County; Alberta F. Coleman, H.D.A., 1930 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Dawson County; T. B. Holker, C.A., 1931 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Dawson County; Alberta Coleman, H.D.A., 1931 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Dawson County; T. B. Holker,, C.A., 1932 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Dawson County; Frances Bellamy, H.D.A., 1932 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Dawson County; T. B. Holker, C.A., 1933 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Dawson County; Gwendolyn Watts, Frances B. Baker, H.D.A.s, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Dawson County; T. B. Holker, Gwendolyn Watts, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Dawson County; Gwendolyn Watts, H.D.A., 1934 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Dawson County; T. B. Holker, C.A., 1935 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Dawson County; Gwendolyn A. Watts, H.D.A., 1935 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Dawson County; T. B. Holker, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Dawson County; Mrs. Gwendolyn Watts Madson, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Dawson County; T. B. Holker, C.A., 1937 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Dawson County; Mrs. Gwendolyn Madson, H.D.A., 1937 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Dawson County; T. B. Holker; Pages 1-124, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Dawson County; T. B. Holker; Pages 125-184, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Dawson County; Gwendolyn W. Madson, H.D.A., 1938 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Dawson County; O. A. Lammers, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Dawson County; Gwendolyn Madson, H.D.A., 1939 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Dawson County; O. A. Lammers, C.A., 1940 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Dawson County; Gwendolyn Madson, H.D.A., 1940 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Dawson County; Oliver A. Lammers, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Dawson County; Mrs. Gwendolyn Madson, H.D.A., 1941 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Dawson County; O. A. Lammers, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Dawson County; Gwendolyn Madson, H.D.A., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Dawson County; O. A. Lammers, C.A., 1943 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Dawson County; Gwendolyn W. Madson, H.D.A., 1943 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Dawson County; O. A. Lammers, C.A., 1944 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Dawson County; Ann Stokan, H.D.A., 1944 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Dawson County; O. A. Lammers, C.A., 1945 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Dawson County; Ann Stokan, Marjean Lasich, H.D.A.s, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Dawson County; O. A. Lammers, C.A., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Dawson County; Glendive - Marjean Lasich, H.D.A., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Dawson County; O. A. Lammers, M. T. Hedegaard, C.A.s, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Dawson County; Marjean Lasich,, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Dawson County; M. T. Hedegaard, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Dawson County; Marjean A. Lasich, H.D.A., 1948 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Dawson County; Marion Hedegaard, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Dawson County; M. T. Hedegaard, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Dawson County; Jeane Fraser, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Dawson County; H. M. Willson, Jeane Fraser, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Dawson County; Howard M. Willson, Jeane Fraser, 1952-1953 (Box 17, Folder 24-25)
  - Dawson County; Howard M. Willson, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Dawson County; Howard Willson, Dale Bergland, Hazel Hinman, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Dawson County; Hazel Hinman, Dale D. Bergland, Howard M. Willson, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Dawson County; Howard Willson, Hazel Hinman, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Dawson County; Hazel Hinman, H.D.A.; Howard Willson, C.A., 1958 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Dawson County; Howard Willson, C.A.; Hazel Hinman, H.D.A., 1959 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Dawson County; Hazel Hinman, Howard Willson, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Dawson County; Hazel Hinman, Dale D. Bergland, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Dawson County; Dale D. Bergland, Hazel Hinman, Carolyn Dufner, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Dawson County; Dale Bergland, George Erickson, Carolyn Dufner, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Dawson County; George Erickson, Dale Bergland, Carolyn Dufner, Sue Kosty, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Dawson County; Dale Bergland, Carolyn Dufner, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
  - Dawson County, 1967-1970 (Box 18, Folder 7-10)
  - Deer Lodge and Powell Counties; J. F. Kreycik, Emergency Report, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Deer Lodge and Powell Counties; Francis L. Niven, C.A., 1940-1944 (Box 18, Folder 12-16)
  - Deer Lodge and Powell Counties; Lin V. Maxwell, C.A., 1945 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Deer Lodge and Powell Counties; J. J. Travis, C.A., 1946 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Deer Lodge and Powell Counties; J. Glenn Jones, C.A., 1947-1954 (Box 18, Folder 19-26)
  - Deer Lodge and Powell Counties; Glenn Jones, Garth Percival, Ramon Nile, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Big Horn County; Leo Kleffner, Harold Strobel, Clementine Sittel, Ada L. King, Howard J. Morton, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Deer Lodge and Powell Counties; Garth D. Percival, John Coston, Betty Donner, Vivienne B. Kintz, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Deer Lodge and Powell Counties; Garth D. Percival, C.A.; Vivienne Kintz, H.D.A., 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 30-31)
  - Deer Lodge and Powell Counties; Garth D. Percival, Harold Strobel, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Deer Lodge and Powell Counties; Harold Strobel, 1961-1966 (Box 18, Folder 33-38)
  - Deer Lodge and Powell Counties, 1967-1970 (Box 18, Folder 39-42)
  - Fallon County; J. O. Hembre, C.A., 1921-1929 (Box 19, Folder 1-9)
  - Fallon County; Alberta Coleman, H.D.A., 1929 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Fallon County; J. O. Hembre, C.A., 1930 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Fallon County; Lucille Kelly, H.D.A., 1930 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Fallon County; J. O. Hembre, C.A., 1931 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Fallon County; Lucille Kelly Everds, H.D.A., 1931 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Fergus County; C. H. Peterson, 1914-1919 (Box 19, Folder 15-20)
  - Fergus County; Nora M. Hott, H.D.A., 1919 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Fergus County; C. H. Peterson, 1920 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Fergus County; Nora M. Hott, 1920 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Fergus County; C. H. Peterson, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Fergus County; C. H. Peterson, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Fergus County; Mrs. May Thomas, H.D.A., 1922 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Fergus County; C. H. Peterson, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Fergus County; Mrs. May Thomas, H.D.A., 1923 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Fergus County; C. H. Peterson, 1924 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Fergus County; Mrs. May Thomas, H.D.A., 1924 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Fergus County; C. H. Peterson, C.A., 1925 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Fergus County; C. H. Peterson, D. B. Noble, C.A.s, 1926 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Fergus County; D. B. Noble, C.A., 1927 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Fergus County; D. B. Noble, C.A., 1928 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Fergus County; Mary Ebersole, H.D.A., 1928 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Fergus County; D. B. Noble, C.A., 1929 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Fergus County; Mary Ebersole, H.D.A., 1929 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Fergus County; W. H. Jones, C.A., 1930 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Fergus County; Mary Ebersole, H.D.A., 1930 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Fergus County; W. H. Jones, C.A., 1931 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Fergus County; Mary Ebersole Conard, H.D.A., 1931 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Fergus County; W. H. Jones, C.A., 1932 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Fergus County; Lucile Smith, H.D.A., 1932 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Fergus County; W. H. Jones, C.A., 1933 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Fergus County; Lucile Smith, H.D.A., 1933 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Fergus County; W. H. Jones, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Fergus County; H. R. Stucky, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fergus County; Florence Michaelson, H.D.A., 1935 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Fergus County; H. R. Stucky, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fergus County; Florence Michaelson, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Fergus County; H. R. Stucky, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Fergus County; Miss Florence Michaelson, Miss Orpha Brown, H.D.A.s, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Fergus County; H. R. Stucky, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Fergus County; Orpha Brown, H.D.A., 1938 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Fergus County; H. R. Stucky; Pages 1-96, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Fergus County; H. R. Stucky; Pages 97-132 and Historical Summary 1-34, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Fergus County; Orpha Brown, H.D.A., 1939 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Fergus County; H. R. Stucky, C.A., 1940 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Fergus County; Orpha Brown, H.D.A., 1940 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Fergus County; H. Ralph Stucky, C.A.; Robert M. Rovig, Acting Agent, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Fergus County; Orpha Brown, Claris Brown, H.D.A.s, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Fergus County; R. M. Rovig, H. R. Stucky, 1942 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Fergus County; Orpha Brown, H.D.A., 1942 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Fergus County; Gerald O. Behimer, C.A., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Fergus County; Orpha B. Spalding, H.D.A., 1943 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Fergus County; Gerald O. Behimer, C.A., 1944 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Fergus County; Orpha Spalding, Marian Moline, H.D.A.s, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Fergus County; G. O. Behimer, C.A., 1945 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Fergus County; Marian Moline, H.D.A., 1945 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Fergus County; O. L. Bunting, C.A., 1946 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Fergus County; Lewistown, Miss Marian Moline, H.D.A., 1946 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Fergus County; O. L. Bunting, C.A., 1947 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Fergus County; Marian Moline, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Fergus County; O. L. Bunting, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Fergus County; Marian Moline, H.D.A., 1948 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Fergus County; O. L. Bunting, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Fergus County; Marian Moline, H. D.A., 1949 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Fergus County; O. L. Bunting, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Fergus County; Marian Moline, H.D.A., 1950 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Fergus County; Keith F. Newby, Mary Willick, 1951-1952 (Box 21, Folder 11-12)
  - Fergus County; Keith F. Newby, Mary W. Baird, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Fergus County; Keith F. Newby, Jeane Fraser, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Fergus County; Keith F. Newby, Duncan A. McRae, Jeane Fraser, Hazel Hinman, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Fergus County; Duncan McRae, Keith Newby, Jeanne Maruska, Effie Enneberg, Louise Guild, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Fergus County; Keith F. Newby, Duncan McRae, Jeanne Maruska, Nita Noel, Patricia George, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Fergus County; Keith F. Newby, C.A.; Duncan McRae, A.A.; Patricia George, H.D.A., 1958 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Fergus County; Keith Newby, C.A.; Duncan McRae, Don Pegg, A.A.s; Pat George, H.D.A., 1959 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Fergus County; Keith F. Newby, James K. Ross, Donald Pegg, Patricia George, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Fergus County; James K. Ross, Donald Pegg, Patricia George, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Fergus County; James K. Ross, Norma Kay Jenni, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Fergus County; James K. Ross, Charles McCay, Patricia George, Norma K. Jenni, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Fergus County; James K. Ross, Patricia George, 1964-1966 (Box 21, Folder 24-26)
  - Fergus County, 1967-1970 (Box 21, Folder 27-30)
  - Flathead County; C. A. Bush, C.A., 1917 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Flathead County; R. B. McKee, C.A., 1918-1919 (Box 21, Folder 32-33)
  - Flathead County; Christine Wood, H.D.A., 1919 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Flathead County; R. B. McKee, C.A., 1920 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Flathead County; Gladys K. Bolon, H.D.A., 1920 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Flathead County; R. B. McKee, C.A., 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 37-38)
  - Flathead County; R. B. McKee, C.A., 1923-1927 (Box 22, Folder 1-5)
  - Flathead County; Frances Smith, H.D.A., 1927 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Flathead County; J. C. Paisley, C.A., 1928 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Flathead County; Frances Smith, H.D.A., 1928 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Flathead County; J. C. Paisley, C.A., 1929 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Report, Flathead County; Frances Smith, H.D.A., 1929 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Flathead County; J. C. Paisley, C.A., 1930 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Flathead County; Grace R. Finucane, H.D.A., 1930 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Flathead County; J. C. Paisely, C.A., 1931 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Flathead County; Grace R. Finucane, H.D.A., 1931 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Flathead County; J. C. Paisley, C.A., 1932 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Flathead County; Grace R. Finucane, H.D.A., 1932 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Emergency Report, Flathead County; R. G. Newell, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Flathead County; R. G. Newell, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Flathead County; R. G. Newell, C.A., 1935 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Flathead County; R. G. Newell, C.A., 1936 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Flathead County; Eleanor Harrer, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Flathead County; R. G. Newell, S. N. Halvorson, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Flathead County; Miss Eleanor Harrer, H.D.A., 1937 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Flathead County; S. N. Halvorson, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Flathead County; Eleanor Harrer, H.D.A., 1938 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Flathead County; S. N. Halvorson, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Flathead County; Eleanor Harrer, Lillian Tubb, H.D.A.s, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Flathead County; Leonard Eliason, C.A., 1940 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Flathead County; Lillian Tubb, H.D.A., 1940 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Flathead County; Leonard Eliason, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Flathead County; Lillian Tubb, H.D.A., 1941 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Flathead County; Leonard Eliason, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 32)